[{"answer": "my friend, you know that, and I know that, but the new General doesn't know it. Or he won't for about an hour and a half", "docId": "whitechristmas.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Yes... isn't he lucky", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "He's awful cute", "docId": "whitechristmas.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " that place, that place wasn't so much", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Where are you going to be for Christmas", "docId": "whitechristmas.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "that place?  What's there", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " I'm not going to keep calling you Miss my friend", "docId": "whitechristmas.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " What a pretty name", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Can't we go tomorrow", "docId": "whitechristmas.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Lady bubble, I have an idea we're going to meet up again sometime", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " Oh, my friend!  What are we going to do", "docId": "whitechristmas.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " How did you find out", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "We don't want anyone else to know", "docId": "whitechristmas.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "How did they know", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Obviously you're going to call the boy after me", "docId": "whitechristmas.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I've been dancing with her!  That's more important!  The baby'll be named after me", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "After you?  I hired my friend!  The baby'll be named after me", "docId": "whitechristmas.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "The hiring was more important!  After me", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I've been dancing with her!  That's more important!  The baby'll be named after me", "docId": "whitechristmas.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "The dancing was more important! After me", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "What's the matter", "docId": "whitechristmas.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "This isn't the way you dance", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "He had no right to do that", "docId": "whitechristmas.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "That doesn't matter", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "You do love him, don't you", "docId": "whitechristmas.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Nothing else matters", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I'm not the least bit worried.  Frankly, this couldn't come at a better time.  They want me to come back to The Carousel again", "docId": "whitechristmas.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Just today, as a matter of fact.  I got a telegram", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "What's the matter", "docId": "whitechristmas.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Don't get what", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I don't get it", "docId": "whitechristmas.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I just don't see it.  You' re skinny, you got a big nose, and you squint", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " Well, surprise.  What brought you to the big city?  And don't say 'a train.'", "docId": "whitechristmas.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": " Some numbers suit you better than others.  What are you doing here", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " If the sock fits, wear it", "docId": "whitechristmas.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "It just started out as a sock", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "my friend!  How are you", "docId": "whitechristmas.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": " my friend", "qsentId": 38}]